

# **PROFILE**

My name is Marlon Bailey, and I am a Computer Science Undergrad at Fairleigh Dickinson with a focus of Web Development. Working at my quick service job I've learned to communicate with people and have gained a sense of leadership. I believe that anything can be done with a sense of urgency. I have experience with developing websites and working with databases.

# CONTACT

PHONE: 862-271-9421

EMAIL: mbaileyjr2003@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Website Development Learning New Techniques Personal Project Endeavors

# MARLON BAILEY JR.

Student

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Garrett Morgan Academy**

September 2017 - June 2021 Salutatorian

# Fairleigh Dickinson University

August 2021 - Current Computer Science Major

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Juicy! Platters Manager

July 2020 - Current Responsible for ensuring store operations are running efficiently. Guest Satisfaction Inventory

#### Juicy Platters Website Developer Internship

April 2022– Current Developed Websites for employee side operations. Responsible for both Front-end and Back-end development. Responsible for database administration. Working in team-oriented environments.

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript
HTML
CSS
Data Entry
Problem Solving
Customer Service
Food Handling
Quick Learner